vajiramandravi.com 2017-12-07

# Privacy and Policy - Vajiram and Ravi

When you use one of our paid products, we track the web pages, and information that has been accessed by you, and store it on our servers. This enables us to track items that you have completed, and those that you need to see.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

If use a feature requiring payment of a fee, we transmit your payment details to our payment service provider for processing. If we encounter a problem with payment, we may review the order information with you and our service provider to resolve it. We do not otherwise disclose your credit card information. We do not share your email address or your personal information with third party marketers.

We use administrative, physical and technical precautions to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information stored on our system. We host the Site at a commercial-grade data center that employs extensive security practices. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our Site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**Information sharing**

Other than the above mentioned sharing of data related to payment details, we only share personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Vajiram and Ravi IAS Study Centre LLP in the following limited circumstances:

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to :

a. Satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request

b. Enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof

c. Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or

d. Protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of vajiramandravi.com or Vajiram and Ravi IAS Study Centre LLP., its users or the public as required or permitted by law. We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users subscribed to a particular product, or the number of users registered on our website. Such information does not identify you individually.

We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to our specified purposes.

How Long Do We Retain User Data?

Currently, we plan to retain user data while an account is active and for at least three years afterward. We may alter this practice according to legal and business requirements. For example, we may lengthen the retention period for some data if needed to comply with law or voluntary codes of conduct. Unless otherwise prohibited, we may shorten the retention period for some types of data if needed to free up storage space.

 **Your Consent to This Policy**

By accessing our website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This document supersedes any prior communication on this topic and reflects the entire and exclusive Privacy Policy for this Site. This Policy is subject to our Terms of Use, which take precedence over any conflicting Policy provision. We may change our Policy by posting a new version of it on our Site.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by writing to us at:

**Address: Vajiram and Ravi IAS Study Centre LLP., 9-B, Bada Bazaar Marg, Old Rajinder Nagar, New Delhi -110060.**
